Who taught you French?
Taught myself.
It's not hard.
Fuckin hell!
Let's go get our money back.
Hey Sébastian. look at this.
Oh. Lieutenant.
Detective.
I got assigned to the homicide
this morning.
Uh. from the car park. I found this.
There was a car idling.
the plates were fake.
But I ran the fingerprints on this -
- and they belong
to a man named Spiro Kreshnik.
Kreshnik as in...
As in Ergon Kreshnik's son.
The Albanian mob
were at the train station this morning.
Fuck… What do they want?
I have no idea.
And there's one more thing -
Was it him?
We agreed we would
keep things professional at work.
We also agreed to be faithful.
so I guess sometimes
we don't keep our promises.
You said there was one more thing.
The victim. The guy on the train.
He doesn't have any fingerprints.
You mean he didn't
leave any fingerprints at the scene?
No. As in. he doesn't
have any fingerprints...
…at all.